

CONTACT

praharajsritam@gmail.com

9438507167

Q Cuttack, India

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/ch -sritam-praharaj-534351153/

SKILLS

Operations Management

* * * * *

Marketing Management

*** * * * ***

Microsoft Office

* * * * *

IBM SPSS

 \diamond \diamond \diamond \diamond

Microsoft Project

*** * * * ***

Adobe Photoshop CC

*** * * * ***

CERTIFICATION

Post Graduate Diploma in Computer Application (2019 - 2020)

Ansys - CAD/CAM Professional

SolidWorks - CAE/CAD Professional

PERSONAL DOSSIER

Address – Cuttack, Odisha, India Date of Birth – 22th Jun, 1997 Marital Status – Single

LANGUAGES

English Hindi Odia



CH. SRITAM PRAHARAJ

RAVENSHAW UNIVERSITY II MBA II OPERATIONS II MARKETING

SUMMARY

A post graduate in Management, a graduate in Mechanical Engineering and a university gold medallist in Master of Business Administration. My professional experience is in the field of National Level Monitoring Project under Ministry of Rural Development. In my current role I am responsible for strengthening all the rural development programmes and ensure the effectiveness, transparency and progress of implementation. I have four Internship experience in country's major leading Organizations.

My core strength lies in my flexibility to work across functions where I have to play a key role in Operations Management and Marketing Management.

EDUCATION

♦ Master of Business Administration

2019 - 2021

Operations Management & Marketing Management

Ravenshaw University, Cuttack

♦ Bachelor of Technology 2015 - 2019

Mechanical Engineering

Parala Maharaja Engineering College, Berhampur

♦ Intermediate in Science 2012 - 2014

Science Education

Kiit Science College, Bhubaneswar

EXPERIENCE

National Level Monitor - Ministry of Rural Development (MoRD)

Aug 2021 - Present

Research and Information Centre for Orissa

Responsible for Monitoring the programmes of the MoRD are being implemented in accordance with the guidelines prescribed by the Ministry, the selection of beneficiaries under the programme has been transparent, unbiased and fair, the assets created are genuine and useful for the community, the views of the villagers on the programmes and their suggestions for improvement.

INTERNSHIPS

Tupperware India Pvt. Ltd.

Jun 2020 - Aug 2020

Executed and delivered a Baseline survey of Tupperware Products by performing market research and Product Feasibility study in the Twin cities of Odisha (Bhubaneswar & Cuttack). Also Carried out a study on company profile, product profile, market awareness, Operational Strategy and distribution network of Tupperware in India.

Hindustan Aeronautics Limited

Jun 2018 - Jul 2018

Carried out a Study on the working principle of jet engine, Manufacturing and different Operational process carried out in Hindustan Aeronautics Limited, Koraput, Odisha.

Sky Rider Institution

May 2018 – Jun 2018

Executed a Study on Ashok Leyland vehicle familiarisation and aggregate overhauling.

Steel Authority of India

Jun 2017 - Jul 2014

Carried out a Study on Manufacturing and Operation management in Rourkela steel plant.

DISSERTATION

Diageo India

Carried out a Study on the Supply Chain Management in Indian Made Foreign Liquor Manufacturing Plant Of M/S Diageo India and understand the Market Demand Forecasting, Production Plan, Sourcing Supplier, Procurement, Manufacturing, Transportation & Logistic, Distribution and Management of Financials.

PROJECT

- Business strategies, supply chain management and logistics management of Amul.
- Operations and marketing strategy of spice-up for managing complex supply chain in large emerging economies.
- Distribution network and supply chain management of Mumbai Dabbawala with six sigma methodology and porter's five forces model.
- Operations Management in steel plant.
- Robot control missile launcher.
- Smart wheel chair cum bed rest for disabled persons.